Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- Steel Labor, 1949-1951 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Steel Labor, 1950; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.9 (1950: Sept.)
  - Item 17: Steel Labor, 1950; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.10 (1950: Oct.)
  - Item 18: Steel Labor, 1950; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.11 (1950: Nov.)
  - Item 19: Steel Labor, 1950; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.12 (1950: Dec.)
  - Item 20: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1951: Jan.)
  - Item 21: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (1951: Feb.)
  - Item 22: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.3 (1951: Mar.)
  - Item 23: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.5 (1951: May)
  - Item 24: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.6 (1951: June)
  - Item 25: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.7 (1951: July)
  - Item 26: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.8 (1951: Aug.)
  - Item 27: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.10 (1951: Oct.)
  - Item 28: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.11 (1951: Nov.)
  - Item 29: Steel Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 121, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.12 (1951: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1952: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1952: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1952: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1952: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.5 (1952: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.7 (1952: July)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.8 (1952: Aug.)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.9 (1952: Sept.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.10 (1952: Oct.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1952; Publication (Box 121, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.12 (1952: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1953: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.2 (1953: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.3 (1953: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.4 (1953: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.5 (1953: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.6 (1953: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.7 (1953: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.8 (1953: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.9 (1953: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.10 (1953: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.11 (1953: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1953; Publication (Box 121, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.12 (1953: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.1 (1954: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.2 (1954: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.3 (1954: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.4 (1954: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.5 (1954: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.6 (1954: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.7 (1954: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.8 (1954: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.9 (1954: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.10 (1954: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.11 (1954: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1954; Publication (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19:no.12 (1954: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.1 (1955: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.2 (1955: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.3 (1955: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.4 (1955: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.5 (1955: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.6 (1955: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.7 (1955: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.8 (1955: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.9 (1955: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.10 (1955: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.11 (1955: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1955; Publication (Box 121, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.20:no.12 (1955: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1956: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.2 (1956: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.3 (1956: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.4 (1956: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.5 (1956: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.6 (1956: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.7 (1956: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.8 (1956: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.9 (1956: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.10 (1956: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.11 (1956: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 122, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.12 (1956: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.1 (1957: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.2 (1957: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.3 (1957: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.5 (1957: May)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.6 (1957: June)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.7 (1957: July)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.8 (1957: Aug.)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.10 (1957: Oct.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.11 (1957: Nov.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1957; Publication (Box 122, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.22:no.12 (1957: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (1958: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.2 (1958: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1958: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.4 (1958: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.5 (1958: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.6 (1958: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.7 (1958: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.8 (1958: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.9 (1958: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.10 (1958: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.10 (1958: Oct.). First Special Convention Issue
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.10 (1958: Oct.). Second Special Convention Issue
  - Item 13: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.11 (1958: Nov.)
  - Item 14: Steel Labor, 1958; Publication (Box 122, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.23:no.12 (1958: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1959: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (1959: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.3 (1959: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.4 (1959: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.5 (1959: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.6 (1959: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.7 (1959: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.8 (1959: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.9 (1959: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.10 (1959: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.11 (1959: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1959; Publication (Box 122, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.24:no.12 (1959: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.1 (1960: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.2 (1960: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.3 (1960: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.4 (1960: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.5 (1960: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.6 (1960: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.4 (1960: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.7 (1960: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.8 (1960: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.9 (1960: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1960; Publication (Box 122, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.25:no.10 (1960: Nov.)
- Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.1 (1961: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.2 (1961: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.3 (1961: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.4 (1961: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.5 (1961: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.6 (1961: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.7 (1961: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.8 (1961: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.9 (1961: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.10 (1961: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.11 (1961: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1961; Publication (Box 123, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.12 (1961: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.1 (1962: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.2 (1962: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.3 (1962: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.4 (1962: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.5 (1962: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.6 (1962: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.7 (1962: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.8 (1962: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.9 (1962: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.10 (1962: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.11 (1962: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1962; Publication (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.27:no.12 (1962: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.1 (1963: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.2 (1963: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.3 (1963: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.4 (1963: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.5 (1963: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.6 (1963: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.7 (1963: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.8 (1963: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.9 (1963: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.10 (1963: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.11 (1963: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1963; Publication (Box 123, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.28:no.12 (1963: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.1 (1964: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.2 (1964: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.3 (1964: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.4 (1964: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.5 (1964: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1964: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.7 (1964: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.8 (1964: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.9 (1964: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.10 (1964: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.11 (1964: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 123, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.29:no.12 (1964: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.1 (1965: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.2 (1965: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.3 (1965: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.4 (1965: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.5 (1965: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.6 (1965: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.7 (1965: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.8 (1965: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.9 (1965: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.10 (1965: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.11 (1965: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 123, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.30:no.12 (1965: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.1 (1966: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.2 (1966: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.3 (1966: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.4 (1966: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.5 (1966: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.6 (1966: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.7 (1966: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.8 (1966: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.9 (1966: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.10 (1966: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1966; Publication (Box 124, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.31:no.12 (1966: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.1 (1967: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.2 (1967: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.3 (1967: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.4 (1967: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.5 (1967: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.6 (1967: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.7 (1967: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.8 (1967: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.9 (1967: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.10 (1967: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.11 (1967: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Steel Labor, 1967; Publication (Box 124, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32:no.12 (1967: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.1 (1968: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.2 (1968: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.3 (1968: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.4 (1968: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.6 (1968: June)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.8 (1968: Aug.)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.10 (1968: Oct.)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.11 (1968: Nov.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1968; Publication (Box 124, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.33:no.12 (1968: Dec.)
- Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.1 (1969: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.2 (1969: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.3 (1969: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.4 (1969: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.5 (1969: May)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.6 (1969: June)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.7 (1969: July)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.8 (1969: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.9 (1969: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.10 (1969: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1969; Publication (Box 124, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.34:no.11 (1969: Nov.)
- Steel Labor, 1970-1971 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.2 (1970: Feb.)
  - Item 2: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.3 (1970: Mar.)
  - Item 3: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.4 (1970: Apr.)
  - Item 4: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.5 (1970: May)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.7 (1970: July)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.8 (1970: Aug.)
  - Item 7: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.10 (1970: Oct.)
  - Item 8: Steel Labor, 1970; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.35:no.12 (1970: Dec.)
  - Item 9: Steel Labor, 1971; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.2 (1971: Feb.)
  - Item 10: Steel Labor, 1971; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.3 (1971: Mar.)
  - Item 11: Steel Labor, 1971; Publication (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36:no.4 (1971: Apr.)